A Guide to the Virginia Room Vertical and Historic Landmark Files, Undated
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- VF - Roads - Dowden Terrace
- VF - Roads - Dulles Access Rd. - (1960-1969)
- VF - Roads - Dulles Access Rd. - (1970-1979)
- VF - Roads - Dulles Access Rd. - (1980 & later)
- VF - Roads - Dulles Access Rd. - (Pre-1960)
- VF - Roads - Dulles Greenway
- VF - Roads - Dulles Toll Rd. - (1969-1979)
- VF - Roads - Dulles Toll Rd. - (1980 & later)
- VF - Roads - Edsal Rd.
- VF - Roads - Fairfax County Parkway
- VF - Roads - Franconia Rd.
- VF - Roads - Fullerton Rd.
- VF - Roads - Gallows Rd.
- VF - Roads - George Washington Memorial Pkwy.
- VF - Roads - Georgetown Pike
- VF - Roads - Great Falls St.
- VF - Roads - History
- VF - Roads - History - Road Orders
- VF - Roads - Hunter Mill Rd.
- VF - Roads - Keene Mill Rd.
- VF - Roads - King's Highway
- VF - Roads - Kirby Rd.
- VF - Roads - Laws
- VF - Roads - Lawyers Rd.
- VF - Roads - Little River Turnpike (Rte. 236)
- VF - Roads - Lockheed Connector
- VF - Roads - Lorton Road
- VF - Roads - Outer Beltway (Proposed)
- HLF - Roads - Ox (Old) Road
- VF - Roads - Pickett Rd.
- VF - Roads - Racial Discrimination Suit (1971-1978)
- VF - Roads - Roberts Road
- VF - Roads - Rolling Rd.
- VF - Roads - Route 1
- VF - Roads - Route 28
- VF - Roads - Route 29-211
- VF - Roads - Route 395 - (Shirley Highway)
- VF - Roads - Route 495 - (Beltway)
- VF - Roads - Route 50
- VF - Roads - Route 595
- VF - Roads - Route 66
- VF - Roads - Route 66 - (Inside the Beltway, 1973 to1974)
- VF - Roads - Route 66 - (Inside the Beltway,1975 to1977)
- VF - Roads - Route 66 - (Inside the Beltway,1978 to 1979)
- VF - Roads - Route 66 - (Inside the Beltway,1980 & later)
- VF - Roads - Route 66 - (Inside the Beltway, Pre-1973)
- VF - Roads - Route 66 - (Outside the Beltway)
- VF - Roads - Route 7
- VF - Roads - Route 95
- VF - Roads - Scenic By-Ways
- VF - Roads - Springfield Interchange (Mixing Bowl)
- VF - Roads - Stone Rd.
- VF - Roads - Street Names
- VF - Roads - Sugarland Run Rd.
- VF - Roads - Telegraph Rd.
- VF - Roads - Tri-County Parkway
- VF - Roads - Uniform Numbering System (1965)
- VF - Roads - Woodlawn Rd.
- HLF - Rokeby
- HLF - Rose Hill Farm (Franconia, Va.).
- HLF - Rosenwald Schools
- HLF - Round Hill (Fort Belvoir, Va.).
- HLF - Royal Oaks (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Ryan Dam (Fairfax Station, Va.).
- HLF - Salisbury Plain (Chantilly Estates)
- HLF - Salona
- HLF - Sangster's Station
- VF - Schools - (1961)
- VF - Schools - (1962)
- VF - Schools - (1963)
- VF - Schools - (1964)
- VF - Schools - (1965)
- VF - Schools - (1966)
- VF - Schools - (1967)
- VF - Schools - (1968)
- VF - Schools - (1969)
- VF - Schools - (1970)
- VF - Schools - (1971)
- VF - Schools - (1972)
- VF - Schools - (1973)
- VF - Schools - (1974)
- VF - Schools - (1975)
- VF - Schools - (1976)
- VF - Schools - (1977)
- VF - Schools - (1978)
- VF - Schools - (1979)
- VF - Schools - (1980)
- VF - Schools - (1981)
- VF - Schools - (1982)
- VF - Schools - (1983)
- VF - Schools - (1984)
- VF - Schools - (1985)
- VF - Schools - (1986)
- VF - Schools - (1987 & later)
- VF - Schools - Bonds
- VF - Schools - Boundaries
- VF - Schools - Buses
- VF - Schools - Censorship
- VF - Schools - Closings
- VF - Schools - Curriculum
- VF - Schools - Curriculum - Language
- VF - Schools - Curriculum - Sex Education
- VF - Schools - Curriculum - Vocational Education
- VF - Schools - Desegregation - Fairfax County
- VF - Schools - Desegregation - Virginia - (1960-1969)
- VF - Schools - Desegregation - Virginia - (1970-1975)
- VF - Schools - Desegregation - Virginia - (1976 & later)
- VF - Schools - Desegregation - Virginia - (Pre-1960)
- VF - Schools - Discrimination
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Idylwood E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Floris E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Floris Colored School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Andrew Chapel
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Annandale E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Baileys Crossroads E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Belle Aire School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Carper School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Chesterbrook E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Dogwood E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Dunn Loring E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Franklin Sherman E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Great Falls School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Groveton E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Hatmark School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Hayfield E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - James Lee E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Legato School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Louise Archer E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Marshall Road E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Oakton E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Quander Road E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Terreset E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Vienna E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Willston E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Lorton E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Colvin Run E. S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Forestville Colored School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Woodlawn E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Fairview E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Herndon E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Kings Park E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Jefferson School
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Colin Powell E. S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Centreville E. S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Crouch
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Navy
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Keene Mill E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Hunters Woods E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Forest Edge E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Lake Anne E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Armstrong E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Crossfield E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Fox Mill E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Forestville E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Sunrise Valley E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Fairfax Villa E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Garfield E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Cherry Run E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Ox Road
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Terra Centre E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Aldrin E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Island Creek E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Whitman E.S.
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Fort Belvoir
- VF - Schools - Elementary - Stratford Landing E.S.
- VF - Schools - Employees - (1960-1969)
- VF - Schools - Employees - (1970-1979)
- VF - Schools - Employees - (1980-1989)
- VF - Schools - Employees - (1990 & later)
- VF - Schools - Employees - Merit Pay
- VF - Schools - Enrollment
- VF - Schools - Federal Aid
- VF - Schools - Health Issues
- VF - Schools - High - South County H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Annandale H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Centreville H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Chantilly H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Edison H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Falls Church H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Fort Hunt H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Groveton H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Hayfield H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Herndon H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Jefferson H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Lake Braddock H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Langley H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Lee H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Luther Jackson H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Madison H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Marshall H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - McLean H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Mount Vernon H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Oakton H.S. (New)
- VF - Schools - High - Oakton H.S. (Old, 1922-1935)
- VF - Schools - High - Robinson H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - South Lakes H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Stuart H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - West Potomac H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - West Springfield H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Woodson H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Westfield H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - Mountain View H.S.
- VF - Schools - High - South Lakes H.S. (folder 2)
- VF - Schools - History
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Benjamin Franklin I.S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Francis Scott Key I.S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Henry Thoreau I.S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Herndon I.S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Whitman I.S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Whittier I.S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Liberty M. S.
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Carson M. S
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Rocky Run Middle
- VF - Schools - Intermediate - Hughes I.S.
- VF - Schools - Kindergarten
- VF - Schools - Newspapers
- VF - Schools - Officials
- VF - Schools - Parochial
- VF - Schools - Private
- VF - Schools - Private - 56 School
- VF - Schools - Private - Madiera School
- VF - Schools - Private - Bethlehem Baptist Academy
- VF - Schools - Private - School for Continuing Education
- VF - Schools - Private - Fairfax Christian Academy
- VF - Schools - Private - Fairfax Christian School (Reston, Va.)
- VF - Schools - Private - Tara Christian School
- VF - Schools - Private - Nysmith School for the Gifted
- VF - Schools - Private - Lake Anne Nursery Kindergarden (LANK)
- VF - Schools - Private - Shoreshim Hebrew School
- VF - Schools - Private - Parkwood School
- VF - Schools - Private - Oakcrest School
- VF - Schools - School Board
- VF - Schools - School Board - Elected
- VF - Schools - School Board - Student Member
- VF - Schools - Sports
- VF - Schools - Students
- VF - Schools - Students - Discipline
- VF - Schools - Students - Dress Codes
- VF - Schools - Students - Drug Use
- VF - Schools - Students - Minorities
- VF - Schools - Students - Rights Policy
- VF - Schools - Students - Smoking
- VF - Schools - Students - Disabilities
- VF - Schools - Testing
- VF - Schools - Vandalism & Violence
- VF - Schools - Year Round
- VF - Seals and Symbols - Fairfax County
- VF - Seals and Symbols - Virginia
- HLF - Sears, Robuck & Co. Houses - (1 of 2)
- HLF - Sears, Robuck & Co. Houses - (2 of 2)
- HLF - Seven Corners Area - Eden Center
- HLF - Seven Corners Area - History
- HLF - Seven Corners Area - Seven Corners Center
- HLF - Seven Hills Lane (#12025) - - Clifton
- HLF - Shady Oak Store
- HLF - Sharon
- HLF - Shepherd's Store - - Mason Neck
- VF - Sheriff - (1971-1972)
- VF - Sheriff - (1973)
- VF - Sheriff - (1974-1977)
- VF - Sheriff - (1978)
- VF - Sheriff - (1979)
- VF - Sheriff - (1980 & later)
- VF - Sheriff - (Pre-1971)
- VF - Sheriff - Offender Aid and Restoration
- HLF - Sherwood Farm
- HLF - Sherwood Hall Lane (#2300) - - Alexandria
- VF - Shopping Centers
- HLF - Shotroff House
- VF - Slavery
- VF - Slavery - Underground Railroad
- HLF - Sleepy Hollow Rd. (#3123)
- HLF - Smith (Jesse) Farm - - Dranesville
- VF - Soils
- VF - South County Center
- HLF - Spies
- HLF - Spies - Ford, Antonia
- HLF - Spies - Ratcliffe, Laura
- VF - Sports
- VF - Sports - Arenas
- VF - Sports - Baseball
- HLF - Spring Bank
- HLF - Spring Glade
- HLF - Spring Hill
- HLF - Springdale Subdivision
- HLF - Springfield - (1960-1969)
- HLF - Springfield - (1970-1979)
- HLF - Springfield - (1980-1989)
- HLF - Springfield - (1990 & later)
- HLF - Springfield - (Broadwater House)
- HLF - Springfield - (Cockburn House)
- HLF - Springfield - (Pre-1960)
- HLF - Springfield - (Pre-1960)
- HLF - Springfield - City Status
- HLF - Springfield - Civic Center
- HLF - Springfield - History
- HLF - Springfield - History
- HLF - Springfield - History (1 of 4)
- HLF - Springfield - History (2 of 4)
- HLF - Springfield - History (3 of 4)
- HLF - Springfield - History (4 of 4)
- HLF - Springfield - Industrial Parks
- HLF - Springfield - Post Office
- HLF - Springfield - Railroad Station
- HLF - Springfield - Springfield Mall
- HLF - Springfield - Springfield Tower
- HLF - Squirrel Hill
- HLF - Stafford Landing
- VF - Sterilizations
- HLF - Stewart House (Chantilly, Va.).
- HLF - Stone Villa Inn - 7910 West Boulevard Drive
- HLF - Stoneleigh
- HLF - Stoneybrooke (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Storm Farm (McLean, Va.).
- HLF - Stratford Landing Subdivision
- HLF - Stratford Landing Subdivision
- HLF - Stuart Mansion (Chantilly, Va.).
- HLF - Stuart's Mill - - Reston/Herndon
- HLF - Subdivisions
- HLF - Sudley (Centreville, Va.).
- HLF - Sully Plantation (Chantilly, Va.). - (1 of 3)
- HLF - Sully Plantation (Chantilly, Va.). - (2 of 3)
- HLF - Sully Plantation (Chantilly, Va.). - (3 of 3)
- HLF - Summit Drive (Taneja House) - - Centreville
- HLF - Sun Valley Subdivision
- HLF - Sunset Hills Farm (Reston, Va.). - Bowman House
- HLF - Sutphin Farm
- HLF - Swink's Mill
- HLF - Sylands
- HLF - Synagogues - Congregation - Olam Tikvah
- HLF - Synagogues - Temple Rodef Shalom - Falls Church
- HLF - Tauxemont [Subdivision]
- HLF - Tauxenent - Doggs Island
- VF - Taverns (Oridinaries)
- VF - Taxation - Pensions
- HLF - Taylor House - 5636 Guinea Road - Fairfax - Young Property
- HLF - Taylor's Tavern (Falls Church, Va.).
- HLF - Thelma's Store (Great Falls, Va.). - (Frank & Thelma Feighery)
- HLF - Thompson House (Navy) - 3418 West Ox Road - Sully
- HLF - Timberlake Park
- HLF - Time Capsule (1977)
- VF - Tobacco
- HLF - Tobey House
- HLF - Toll House (Georgetown Pike)
- HLF - Tops Drive-in
- HLF - Tower House (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Tower Lawn
- HLF - Towlston Grange (Great Falls, Va.).
- HLF - Towns - (Extinct & Dormant)
- HLF - Trailer Parks
- VF - Transportation
- VF - Transportation - Buses
- VF - Transportation - Buses - A, B, & W Bus Lines
- VF - Transportation - Buses - W, V, & M Bus Lines
- VF - Transportation - Buses - Colonial Transit Co.
- VF - Transportation - Buses - CUE
- VF - Transportation - Buses - Fairfax Connector
- VF - Transportation - Buses - Jitney Bus Service
- VF - Transportation - Buses - Reston Commuter Bus
- VF - Transportation - Buses - Shirley Highway Express
- VF - Transportation - Buses - Link Trolley
- VF - Transportation - Carpooling
- VF - Transportation - Commuting
- VF - Transportation - Federal Rate of Mileage Reimbursement
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Orange Line - (Pre-1971)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Orange Line - (1971-1975)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Orange Line - (1976-1980)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Orange Line - (1981 & later)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Yellow/Blue Line - (Pre-1971)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Yellow/Blue Line - (1971-1975)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Yellow/Blue Line - (1976-1980)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Yellow/Blue Line - (1981-1985)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Yellow/Blue Line - (1985 & later)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Coalition for Metro Accountability
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Equipment
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Parking
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (Pre-1969)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1969)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1970)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1971)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1972)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1973)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1974)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1975)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1976)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1977)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1978)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1979)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1980)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1981)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1982)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1983)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1984)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1985)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1986)
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Fares
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Policies - Fairfax City
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Policies - Fairfax County
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Policies - Virginia
- VF - Transportation - Metro - History
- VF - Transportation - Metro - History - Chronologies
- VF - Transportation - Metro - Silver Line
- VF - Transportation - Metro - (1987-Present)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (Pre-1972)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1972)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1973)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1974)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1975)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1976)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1977)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1978)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1979)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - (1980-1985)
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - Fares
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - Shelters
- VF - Transportation - Metrobus - Springfield Garage
- VF - Transportation - Monorails & Skyways
- VF - Transportation - Northern Virginia Transportation Commission
- VF - Transportation - Taxes
- VF - Transportation - Taxis
- HLF - Treasure
- VF - Trees
- VF - Trivia
- HLF - Trott Cabin
- HLF - Tudor Hall
- HLF - Tulip Hill - - McLean
- HLF - Tunlaw
- HLF - Turberville/Ball Tract
- HLF - Turkey Run Farm (McLean, Va.).
- HLF - Turley Hall (Chantilly, Va.).
- HLF - Turner Dairy Farm - - Dranesville
- HLF - Twinbrooks - Accontink Road - Lorton
- HLF - Tysons Corner - (1971-1980)
- HLF - Tysons Corner - (1981-1990)
- HLF - Tysons Corner - (1991 & later)
- HLF - Tysons Corner - (Pre-1971)
- HLF - Tysons Corner - Galleria at Tysons II
- HLF - Tysons Corner - History
- HLF - Tysons Corner - Rotunda
- HLF - Tysons Corner - Tycon Towers
- HLF - Tysons Corner - Tysons Corner Center
- HLF - Tysons Corner - Westgate/Westpark
- HLF - Union Farm (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Union Mills (Clifton, Va.). - History
- VF - United States Geological Survey
- HLF - Upper Pohick Community Hall (Springfield, Va.).
- VF - USS Fairfax County
- VF - USS Herndon
- VF - Utilities
- VF - Utilities - Electricity
- VF - Utilities - Gas
- VF - Utilities - Telephone
- VF - Utilities - Water
- HLF - Vale Community Center
- HLF - Vaucluse
- HLF - Victorian Farmhouse
- HLF - Vienna - Black History
- HLF - Vienna - Church Street
- HLF - Vienna - City Status
- HLF - Vienna - Cook House
- HLF - Vienna - DeRamus Property - 9416 Atwood Road
- HLF - Vienna - Deshayes House
- HLF - Vienna - Flags, Symbols, Etc…
- HLF - Vienna - Freeman House
- HLF - Vienna - Government
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1960-1964)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1965-1966)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1967-1969)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1970-1972)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1973-1975)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1976-1979)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1980-1989)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (1990-1999)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (2000 & later)
- HLF - Vienna - Government - (Pre-1960)
- HLF - Vienna - Historic Houses
- HLF - Vienna - Historic Vienna, Inc. - Historic Vienna, Inc.
- HLF - Vienna - History
- HLF - Vienna - History - Civil War
- HLF - Vienna - Malcolm Heights
- HLF - Vienna - Officials
- HLF - Vienna - Officials
- HLF - Vienna - Ordinances
- HLF - Vienna - Pleasant Place
- HLF - Vienna - Police
- HLF - Vienna - Railroad Station
- HLF - Vienna - Restaurants
- HLF - Vienna - Restaurants - Vienna Inn
- HLF - Vienna - Roads
- HLF - Vienna - Salsbury Spring
- HLF - Vienna - Sister City (Ceret, France)
- HLF - Vienna - Town Hall
- HLF - Vienna - Town Library
- HLF - Vienna - Virginia Center
- HLF - Vienna - Windover Heights
- HLF - Vienna - Windover Heights Historic District
- HLF - Virginia City
- VF - Virginia Constitution
- HLF - Virginia Hills (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Virginia Nonimportation Association Broadside 1770
- HLF - Virginia Run [Subdivision]
- VF - Voting & Elections
- HLF - Walney
- HLF - Walnut Hill
- HLF - Walnut Hill/Grove - 2603 Faber Court - Falls Church
- HLF - Waple's Mill
- HLF - Waple's Mill Area
- HLF - Washington's Grist Mill - 5514 Mount Vernon Highway - Mount Vernon
- VF - Waste - Hazardous
- VF - Waste - Recycling
- VF - Waste - Sewage
- VF - Waste - Solid - Landfills - Lorton
- VF - Waste - Solid - Landfills - Fairfax Station
- VF - Waste - Solid - Landfills - Fort Belvoir
- VF - Waste - Solid - Landfills - Telegraph Road
- VF - Waste - Solid - Landfills - Stump Dump, Inc.
- VF - Waste - Solid - Landfills - I-66 Landfill
- VF - Waste - Solid - (Pre-1970)
- VF - Waste - Solid - (1970-1979)
- VF - Waste - Solid - (1980-1989)
- VF - Waste - Solid - (1990-1999)
- VF - Waste - Solid - Incinerator
- VF - Water Supply - (1971-1973)
- VF - Water Supply - (1974-1975)
- VF - Water Supply - (1976-1980)
- VF - Water Supply - (1981-1990)
- VF - Water Supply - (1991-2000)
- VF - Water Supply - (2001- )
- VF - Water Supply - (Pre-1971)
- HLF - Watering Trough - Fort Hunt Road - Mount Vernon
- VF - Weather
- VF - Weather - Acid Rain
- VF - Weather - Cold
- VF - Weather - Drought
- VF - Weather - Heat
- VF - Weather - Hurricane
- VF - Weather - Rain
- VF - Weather - Snow
- VF - Weather - Tornadoes
- HLF - Weights and Measures
- HLF - Wellington
- HLF - Westbrook Drive (Log House)
- HLF - White Cottage (Lipscomb)
- HLF - White House Replica - - Fairfax
- HLF - White, Elijah House
- HLF - Wiehle - History
- HLF - Wiehle House
- HLF - Wilton Hall
- HLF - Windy Hill Farm - Bois De Gosses
- HLF - Wine (William) House - 1416 Crowell Road - Vienna
- HLF - Winfield Farm
- HLF - Wolf Run Shoals Camp (Civil War)
- HLF - Wolf Trap Area - History
- HLF - Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts
- HLF - Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts - (2 of 2)
- VF - Women
- HLF - Woodaman House
- HLF - Woodberry
- HLF - Woodbury House - 10307 Saddle View Court - Hunter Mill
- HLF - Woodlawn Plantation (Alexandria, Va.).
- HLF - Wrenn House (Chantilly, Va.).
- HLF - Wright Houses in Fairfax County - (See also: Pope-Leighey House, Marsden House)
- HLF - Zion Road Community - (Sideburn Area)